<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>COVID-19 on Digital River</title>
    <link>https://DigitalRiver.blog/tags/covid-19/</link>
    <description>Recent content in COVID-19 on Digital River</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2020 00:00:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://DigitalRiver.blog/tags/covid-19/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>After COVID-19: Rebuilding America (and the World) - Starts With You Today</title>
      <link>https://DigitalRiver.blog/post/2020-04-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2020 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://DigitalRiver.blog/post/2020-04-10/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;tl;dr&lt;/strong&gt; COVID-19 has impacted all of us in some shape or form. The time to rebuild America (and the World) starts today with each and every one of us. It is time to wake the sleeping giant in each and everyone of us and do our part in this RECOVER - REBOOT - REBUILD process.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;img &#xA;    &#xA;        src=&#34;https://DigitalRiver.blog/img/2020/04/10/covid-19_2Rs.png&#34; &#xA;    &#xA;    &#xA;        alt=&#34;COVID-19 : RECOVER, REBOOT, REBUILD&#34;&#xA;    &#xA;     &#xA;        width=&#34;250&#34; &#xA;    &#xA;    &#xA;     &#xA;        align=&#34;left&#34; &#xA;    &#xA;    &#xA;        class=&#34;alignleft round-img-border imgframe-right-pad&#34; &#xA;    &#xA;    &gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Today, (as I reflect on the pandemic) I am constantly reminded that we are yet to see the peak of this impact; with no end at sight, no light at the end of the tunnel, no reason yet to celebrate. My mind goes through a flood of emotions, thoughts, memories, visuals, events and sounds as I am continuously reminded of the ghostly silent voices of the dead. The casualties of this war where the enemy isn&amp;rsquo;t a faceless soldier from afar but someone very near and close to us. A self-inflicted wound. A child and product of our own upbringing! Our own harvest and reaping! This article is my attempt to capture it all and to find some solace and grace through it all.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
